    
	{
		"question": "The address stored in the pointer variable is of type?",
		"options" : [
				"int",
				"float",
				"array",
				"string"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option1"
	}$
	{
		"question": "The operators . , !! , < , = if arranged in ascending order of precedence reads?",
		"options" : [
				".,!!,<,=",
				"=,<,!!,.",
				"=,!!,<,.",
				"<,!!,=,."
		],
		"correct_answer":"option3"
	}$
	{
		"question": "Char *s[10] defines an array of ___________",
		"options" : [
				"None",
				"String to pointer",
				"Pointer to string",
				"Both pointers to strings and strings to pointers"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option3"
	}$
	{
		"question": "Which header file should be included to use functions like malloc() and calloc()?",
		"options" : [
				"Dos.h",
				"Alloc.h",
				"Stdlib.h",
				"Memory.h"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option3"
	}$
	{
		"question": "What gets printed? printf(\"%d\",4 ?:8);",
		"options" : [
				"8",
				"4",
				"Null",
				"Compiler error"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option4"
	}$
	{
		"question": "Which keyword is used for coming out of recursion?",
		"options" : [
				"Break",
				"Return",
				"Exit",
				"All the above"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option2"
	}$
	{
		"question": " How many tokens are there in the following?       if(csi==100);",
		"options" : [
				"6",
				"7",
				"5",
				"4"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option2"
	}$
	{
		"question": "C programming:the given expression P-=Q+1 is same as",
		"options" : [
				"P=P-Q-1",
				"P=P-Q+1",
				"P=-P+Q+1",
				"None"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option1"
	}$
	{
		"question": "A pointer is a C which has not been initialized is know as:",
		"options" : [
				"Far pointer",
				"Void pointer",
				"Null pointer",
				"Wild pointer"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option4"
	}$
	{
		"question": "Which of the following does not represent a valid storage class in C?",
		"options" : [
				"Static",
				"Union",
				"Extern",
				"Automatic"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option2"
	}$
	{
		"question": "When fopen() is not able to open a file, then it returns",
		"options" : [
				"Complier dependent",
				"Run time error",
				"EOF",
				"Null"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option1"
	}$
	{
		"question": "How will you free the allocated memory?",
		"options" : [
				"Delete(var-name);",
				"Free(var-name);",
				"Remove(var-name);",
				"Dealloc(var-name);"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option2"
	}$
	{
		"question": "What will be x in the following c code? #include void main() {  int x; }",
		"options" : [
				"Integer variable",
				"Static variable",
				"Registered variable",
				"Global variable"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option1"
	}$
	{
		"question": "Which of the following cannot be static in C?",
		"options" : [
				"Variables",
				"Structures",
				"Functions",
				"None"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option4"
	}$
	{
	"question": "What is the output of the following?   #include int main() { char ch; if(ch = printf(\"\") printf(\"It matters\"); else printf(\"It doesn't matter\"); return 0; }",
	"options": [
		"It matters",
		"It doesn't matter",
		"Run time error",
		"Nothing"
	],
	"correct_answer": "option2"
    }
	$
	{
	"question": "What is the output of the following?   #include int main() { char ch; if(ch = printf(\"\") printf(\"It matters\"); else printf(\"It doesn't matter\"); return 0; }",
	"options": [
		"It matters",
		"It doesn't matter",
		"Run time error",
		"Nothing"
	],
	"correct_answer": "option2"
}
$
	{
		"question": "Which of the following is not a standard C Library?",
		"options" : [
				"Errno.h",
				"Setjmp.h",
				"Signal.h",
				"Retarg.h"
		],
		"correct_answer":"option4"
	}